crowdtap.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy

**Crowdtap, Inc.**  (“Crowdtap”, “Company”, “we” or “us”), the operator of the www.crowdtap.com (“Site”) and **Crowdtap web platform and membership program** (“Platform”), is committed to preserving the privacy of those who visit the Site and become members of the Platform (“Members”). Crowdtap has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to helping you better understand what information we collect about you and what may happen to that information during your visit to the Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected at this Site. By using or accessing the Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy.  **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE**.

 **Information Collected**

When using the Site, in order to utilize some of the services, you may be asked to provide, or you may choose to upload, certain personally identifiable information about yourself ("Personal Information"). Personal Information can include your name, occupation, photo, email address, address, phone number(s), Facebook profile, Twitter handle, selected interests, gender, or date of birth. Please note that Personal Information may also include personally identifiable information you voluntarily provide when you take a survey or a poll or enter a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion.

In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other data, and may aggregate any Personal Information collected, such as demographic information, in a manner which does not identify any one person ("Aggregate Information"). Survey answers and influencer scores that are not connected to Personal Information may also constitute Aggregate Information.

 **Information Usage**

We may share your Personal Information with our brand clients (“Brands”), affiliates, charity partners, technical consultants, third party auditors or other third parties who compile the Aggregate Information, make our Site available, enhance its functionality or provide associated services and/or process your orders and/or deliver content, samples, supplies, products, or services. For example, we may share your Personal Information with a vendor to fulfill any incentive or reward which you have elected to receive and that vendor may forward your email address to a third party to redeem any rewards. You may opt-out at any time in accordance with the "Terminating Membership" section below.

We may use your Aggregate Information to do such things as operate our Site and enhance our Site, and for market research purposes. We may share Aggregate Information with our Brands, affiliates, charity partners and other third parties for advertising, promotional and other purposes. Individual answers from you to questions within polls or missions marked as “confidential” may be shared with our affiliates, Brands and business partners but those answers will not be labeled with, or linked to, your Personal Information.

Your user name, zip code, Crowdtap Points, profile photo, badges and levels earned, and some of your activity may be shared with other Crowdtap users within the Site, including without limitation publication in a live feed of ongoing activities and leader boards. You may also see such information related to other Members when logged into the Site.

On the Site, Crowdtap, our Brands and some of our business partners will have the ability to contact you regarding missions or rewards for which you qualify. We hereby disclaim all responsibility and liability should a Brand contact you directly by virtue of your posting of Personal Information on the Site in a section of the Site where it was not explicitly requested or outside of the Site where it may be viewable and/or accessible by Brands (e.g., contact information listed within feedback you provide, information on your Facebook profile linked to your Crowdtap account, or an email address you provided directly to a Brand).

We will never rent or sell your Personal Information to any third party without your consent. Please note that we reserve the right to and may disclose Personal Information about you in response to (a) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (b) any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena; (c) if required by law, regulation or order; or (d) to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Site rules or policies, or the rights of third parties to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. Please also note that we reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information and other information to our successors in business and purchasers of site assets. Information obtained in connection with the Site may be intermingled with and used by us in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than the Site, including both offline and online sources. In addition, we may use the information you provide to comply with regulatory monitoring and reporting obligations imposed by Brands in connection with adverse events. In such instances, we may require further information from you in addition to Personal Information to comply with such regulatory monitoring and reporting obligations. Such information may be provided to the relevant Brand and governmental authorities.

 **Registration**

In order to use the Site, a Member must first provide the information requested on the "Registration" page. During registration, a Member may be required to provide his/her contact information (including, but not limited to, name, email address, and postal address), Facebook user information, additional psychographic information, and information needed for delivering Crowdtap rewards once redeemed. This information is used to notify the Member about new missions, Crowdtap rewards, and changes in Crowdtap reward offerings. In addition, we may ask Members to provide legitimate proof of address. Proof of address is required in order to guard Crowdtap from fraudulent activities. This information is also used for shipping purposes for prizes redeemed by Members.

 **Your Account**

Once you become a Member of the Platform, you will receive a password and an account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, as well as your Facebook username and password which may be used through Facebook Connect. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose such password or account information to any third parties. If you choose to share this information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account information and password and therefore should review each third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your account password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. Furthermore, you are entirely responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You agree to immediately notify Crowdtap of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security known to you.

 **Cookies**

The Site uses cookies to keep track of your activity on the Site and enhance your experience on the Site. We also use cookies to save your account information and password. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas or functions on the Site.

 **Clickstream**

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to the Site. We may collect and use clickstream data as a form of Aggregate Information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Site, how visitors navigate throughout the Site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will be used to improve our Site and our services. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not intentionally contain any Personal Information.

 **Security**

Crowdtap will not be liable for disclosures of your Personal Information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. We have undertaken all commercially reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized Internet access to visitor data retained in our servers, however, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, Crowdtap cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or any information provided online, and you do so at your own risk. You must accept all risks associated with any data transmission, including the risk that your personal information may be intercepted in transit. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

 **Special Offers**

Members may receive emails containing information regarding their activities in the Program, new missions, contests and sampling opportunities, or other news from Crowdtap if they have opted in.  "Opted in" means the Member has indicated his or her willingness to receive such emails from Crowdtap and has not communicated his/her preference to the contrary, which can be done through his/her account settings.

 **Crowdtap Site and Service Announcements**

Members will receive email announcements when they become eligible for rewards.  Members are not able to unsubscribe or “opt out” of these emails; without them, you would not be able to receive rewards for which you become eligible.  If you do not wish to receive these emails, please see the "Terminating Membership" section in this Privacy Policy. 

Under certain circumstances Crowdtap may need to contact some or all Members in order to make an important announcement about the Site or Platform changes. Members are not able to unsubscribe or "opt out" of these announcements because they may contain very important information regarding their accounts. Before these measures are taken, however, Crowdtap will post information regarding changes directly on the Site. Crowdtap reserves the right to contact Members to correct account errors or to supply important information Crowdtap deems relevant.

 **Correction/Updating Personal Information**

Members are able to change their personal information at any time by editing the information entered on their profile pages.

 **Protection for Children Age/Residency Requirements**

This Site is not intended for users under the age of 13, and we have no intention of collecting Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Where appropriate, we take reasonable measures to inform children not to submit such information to our Site. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. You must be at least 13 years old, be a United States resident, and have a valid email address to join the Platform. Registration and participation in a mission is open to individuals only (no corporations or other legal entities). Each individual who registers on Crowdtap or participates in a mission is responsible for providing the information requested and for updating any such information to insure its accuracy. Receipt of inaccurate or misleading information will adversely affect the ability of Crowdtap to operate a mission and provide services to Brands required by Members and participants. In this regard, Crowdtap reserves the right to terminate a Member’s membership in Crowdtap or participation in a mission if misleading or intentionally incorrect personal information is provided. Crowdtap reserves the right to modify or discontinue a mission at any time with or without notice to members. Crowdtap will not be liable to any Member or any third party should Crowdtap exercise its right to modify or discontinue a mission or membership.

 **Bulletin Boards and Chat Areas**

You should be aware that Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit online may be viewed and used by others. Users of the Site are solely responsible for the content of messages they post online including on public forums. These forums include but are not limited to chat rooms on our Site or other websites, bulletin boards, blogs, social media web pages or other publicly accessible forums which may be viewed and used by anyone with access to such forums. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose Personal Information within a public forum that user information may be collected and used by others. The Site is unable to control such uses of your Personal Information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

 **Links to Third Party Sites**

Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this Privacy Policy.

 **Export of Data**

Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

 **Changes to Policy**

We reserve the right to change, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. All information posted on the Site is subject to change without notice. In addition, this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to, how we use your Personal Information, may be changed by us at any time without prior notice. We will make such changes by posting them here. You should check this page for such changes frequently. Your continued use of the Site after such changes are made conclusively demonstrates your acceptance of those changes. You may "opt out" of this Site, including, but not limited to, receiving communications from us and/or sharing your Personal Information with us, at any time. In order to "opt out" please see the "Terminating Membership" section in this Privacy Policy. Please note that we are not responsible for removing your Personal Information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **Terminating Membership  
**  
You or Crowdtap may terminate your membership in the Platform for any reason with or without cause at any time and effective immediately. Crowdtap will not be liable to you or any third party for termination of the Platform or Site. You may terminate your membership by contacting us or by using the “terminate membership” function if available. Upon terminating your membership, Crowdtap, will remove the following Personal Information from Crowdtap’s active database: Crowdtap password, member profile, full name, address (except for zip code), email address, other contact information, Facebook account information, Twitter account information, and profile photo. Any of your Personal Information or activity history that is not deleted will be attached to either your username or a unique database ID, not to your personally identifiable information.

 **Site Terms and Conditions**

Use of this Site is governed by, and subject to, the legal notices contained in Crowdtap’s Terms of Service. Your use, or access, of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions. Use of the Platform is governed by Crowdtap’s Membership Agreement.

Void where prohibited by law.

 **Comments and Questions:** If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may [contact us](mailto:support@crowdtap.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry).

MAIL   
Crowdtap Inc.   
625 Broadway   
5th Floor   
New York, NY 10012

EMAIL   
contact us  

Effective Date: This privacy policy is effective and was last updated on March 14st, 2016.
